Nightitten months will be the same long time
Everything falls down So let's go
Make it fun!
The wind lung is somewhere
It came across north side
Wherefore wherever they come
目奪われて 音を立て、ときめきの予感 真っ白な秘めた気持ちが色づいてゆく
最後は君と紡いでいく未来 今はまだ財探りで迷っても
Hopeful, 描き出す 光
花色の明日が呼んでる
道知るってなくたって
不安だね
分け合って
君がいるいつだって
ほら笑って
High five!
コフィン コスプレー
That's it.
After we wrap up the Coffin cosplay, I'm gonna tell him.
I have no choice. I have to.
I have to tell Gojo that I love him.
So the big day is finally here.
Once we finish, I've gotta tell him that I love him.
No ifs, ands, or buts.
I said I would do it, so I'm gonna.
Hey Gojo, one thing.
Don't laugh, but I wanted to tell you that...
That I...
Love...
YOU!
Fart corny to the max!
Good morning.
Morning?
Uh, come in.
Right.
Let's start on your makeup.
Kay.
Oh, yeah.
I already put on foundation.
Oh, that's super helpful.
Thank you.
Kitagawa?
Huh?
Could you do me a favor and look up a little higher for me?
Perfect.
Hold it just like that.
I think I'll start with your eyes today.
Uh-huh.
Do I have it in me?
Can I confess for realsies?
Uh-huh.
Morning, everyone.
Hey, hey, girly pop.
Morning, Suzuka.
The date is finally here.
The whole studio is pitch black.
Yep.
I figured if we kept it simple, then the gore could really pop.
Hard core?
I thought about renting a church, but the focus of this shoot should be on the people, not the background.
And the darkness reflects Mira's mental state.
I guess so.
Hey, is Akira here?
She just changed and is chilling in the shower.
Screen fricking accurate!
Looks great.
I think Suzuka made those for us.
I should change.
We got a dressing room around here.
Out the door and to the left.
Mia and the others are changing right now.
Last one in, Zara!
Next!
Uh-huh.
Almost forgot.
Since we only have one dressing room, you'll have-
AAAAAAAH!
I'm sorry!
Force of habit, I guess.
When I lived at home, it was no big deal to change in front of my sis.
That makes sense.
If it really doesn't bother you...
By all means, continue.
You good girl.
EEEEH!
WOOOOOOO!
You're literally sister Mira right now, Shinju!
And your sister Claire is perfection, Juju.
I'm glad to see you aren't dreading this, as well.
I can't believe the past two days of my life have been so jam-packed with gorgeous Juju cosplay!
Endless dream of a woos!
Crying will just smear your makeup.
I'm ready! The room is all yours.
Hey, Miyako! Good morning!
You can have the changing room now, Maureen.
Shinju, let's get the girls wrapped.
Right!
Is it too tight? If it gets hard to breathe, then we'll take a break.
Feels fine now.
Tis a risky game.
Her boobs could explode out of there like when we cosplayed Blaze.
So I can be on Boobwatch.
Thank you so much!
You're just gonna stare at her bazongas?
Done. Let's get creepy.
Once you put your cosplay on, we can finally bring this dream into the real world!
Yay!
You're a genius.
When you shoot from above, you can't tell that they're different heights at all!
Right?
Height's no problem when you have a ladder.
They look so natural.
Can I get a sneak peek?
Same here!
Sure! Come check our work.
Maureen and I look like we're the exact same height!
Ha ha! This rules! You're a legit wizard, Suzuka!
Oh, you're too sweet! Thank you, Maureen!
The height thing is cool for sure!
But how do our cosplays look? Do we look like the characters?
Hells yeah!
Is this the fake blood the studio prepared?
Mm-hmm. It's really thick, so I'll thin it out with water.
They achieved the perfect shade of deep red.
Great work! Now let's move on to the dinner scene.
Kay!
Let the blood path begin.
Time to say bye-bye, Mia!
Bye-bye! I am the one who dies first, after all.
I hope my body's tasty.
You're too energetic for a dead girl.
Ha ha ha ha!
Oh, but wait!
I still have to plate up the crops and big blood,
so you guys sit tight.
Okay!
Sure thing!
Soup's almost up, everybody!
Don't look down.
Under no circumstances look down.
It kind of looks like a beef stew with big chunks of meat.
Don't look down.
It's so true!
Shiju, yours has an ear in it!
Don't look down!
I'm so lifelike!
Huh?
Do I have the cutest secret admirer or something?
Because you're like Toad staring me down?
Your dumb face is simply the lesser of two evils, okay?
Whoa, that looks delish!
It's papier-mache.
A cake?
What is it for?
I got so scared that I couldn't finish the game.
I don't know the whole story.
Does it get even worse?
Watch out!
What is it for?
Thank you for the meal.
Sajuna, dear.
I have a secret.
I added veggies to the soup that you don't typically like.
Huh?
The truth is, I added them to yesterday's lasagna too.
And to lunch as well.
I pureed them so you wouldn't notice.
And you didn't, did you?
Well?
Did it taste good?
Huh?
You're kidding me.
An eyeball?
Save me, Mom.
What a detail.
That's sick!
Freaky.
Now that's a tone shift.
Super cute.
Wait, you took a picture of me?
You look so nice, I had to!
This is the scariest one.
Never mind, this one's worse.
Yeah, it'll be less creepy once we edit her face out.
I really love the title screen.
I was just so happy.
It's a little embarrassing to admit it to all of you out loud.
But during the shoot, as I looked into your faces,
I got to step inside this world that means so much to me.
I still can't believe I got to live in Sister Mira's shoes for a while.
It felt like I was dreaming.
The nuns sitting around the table every day.
That special family gathered together must have made Sister Mira so happy.
I know my heart felt so full, it could burst.
Sad, sad!
Sister Mira and I aren't the same person exactly because
I would never chop you up and eat you for dinner!
Aren't you glad you joined in instead of just watching this time?
Yes!
Hey, Xingjiu.
Now that we're done, let me help you loosen up your wrap.
Thanks, that would be awesome.
I know it's still a bit early, but once Aki is done washing off the blood,
let's start cleaning up.
Yeah, clean up will take a while.
There you are.
I've been looking for you.
Do you want to check out the photos with the others?
No, not in the slightest.
I was surprised when you agreed to be in the group.
Since you don't like horror stuff,
I just figured that you would set this one out.
I hate it.
Huh?
And this shoot has only reaffirmed that.
Then why'd you agree to participate at all?
You didn't have to.
I knew that I could suffer through a few hours.
Wakana Gojo.
Just who do you think I am?
Well, you're a great cosplayer with a big following?
Wrong!
I'm Shinju's big sister!
Huh?
Did you see her eyes?
How could I refuse?
I'm responsible for my own dreams,
and I have you, and Miyako,
and the rest of these new allies to help me out.
But I'm the only one who can see to it that Shinju's dreams come true.
Hmm.
Such a big sister.
Were you listening to me?
That's what I just said!
I'm not myself right now.
And there's nothing I can do to calm down or change my surroundings.
When my emotions are compromised like this,
I don't want to be around people.
I need to be by myself.
And yet...
I despise the fact I had fun today.
I'm done with group cosplays.
No, no more!
I'm far better off when I'm dressed up as a cutesy magical girl
I'll grow them completely.
Are you okay?
She's not okay!
Did you scare her to death?
You should try drinking some water!
Air!
She needs fresh air!
It feels much better, loosen like this.
Breathing is key.
I'mma use some eyedrops, then I'll join you.
Okay.
Sorry, excuse me.
You're fine, no worries.
Your collar's undone.
Just a sec.
Thank you, I didn't notice.
Come to think of it,
we shot partner scenes of almost everyone
except Akira and Maureen.
Maybe Suzuka just forgot.
Oh, hey!
You're sweet to wait on me, Shinju.
Um...
Huh?
We forgot to shoot your partner scene.
If it's okay with you, I'll take it now.
I absolutely love the scene where Sister Rose and Sister Sophia start fighting and bring out the scissors.
We have to get that picture.
Just let me grab my camera!
Hang on!
Shinju!
What do I do?
If I tell Shinju we can't because Akira hates my guts,
it'll totally bum her out.
But there's also no shot Akira's willing to take a pic with me.
I've got to stop this.
Funny story, bestie!
Uh, Akira actually hates me, so...
No, I mean, she...
I don't want to be her buddy.
I don't want to talk to her.
I don't want her near me.
I just...
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I invited her to join without realizing you had beef.
It's not that...
Huh?
The truth is...
She, uh...
is my...
princess.
Prin-cess?
Your princess is...
who?
You're kidding.
That's Maureen.
Over the summer,
Suzuka texted me a pic.
My one thought was,
wow, she's a real princess.
Wakuna did not follow.
I'm going now, princess.
It was like her picture reached out and touched my heart.
It was perfect.
I fell for every teeny tiny detail.
She was so beautiful.
I couldn't take it.
I agree.
That photo is one of her very best.
Inoue's lighting was great,
and her expression is spot on.
That photo would have been nothing without your costume!
Don't sell yourself short, dammit!
Forgive me!
You're a super fan, huh?
I bet it would make Maureen's day if you told her that.
Uh-uh.
What's the deal?
There's no way I could ever talk to her.
I can't even look her in the eye.
I'd freeze up and sound like a total loser if I tried.
See?
Now you get it.
I can't be around her.
I am a creep.
I can't let my perfect princess see me when I'm like this.
Even at the park.
The very first time she said hi.
Hello.
Hello?
What the hell was I thinking?
I was such a creeper!
Uh, please!
I promise you were completely fine!
You weren't weird at all!
She needs help.
I was fighting to keep my cool in there.
Learning about photography made her so happy.
I couldn't believe how cute she was in real life!
The photos only captured a fraction of my princess's Incredibles!
That's a mad RBF.
It's just...
To be honest, I didn't think anything good would ever happen to me.
But now...
I'm happy every single day.
And having my princess is part of the reason why.
Her smile just keeps me going somehow.
I would do anything to repay her for the light she brought into my life since I saw her photo.
I can't do the group.
Just thinking about being in the same room as her makes me so nervous that I could throw up!
Well, don't do that!
If we had to take a photo together, I'd fall my eyes out in time right there!
You guys don't want to see me break down like this again, do you?
Nope.
One meltdown is more than enough.
Ouch!
Himuno was brutally honest!
This is the end!
Interrupted Jack!
I know that banshee!
The death knell!
I knew it!
Huh?
Are you talking about Shinju or me?
You totally hate my guts, don't you?
Sorry!
We couldn't tell you before!
No!
She loves you!
Exactly!
Apparently you're Akira's best girl!
Her what?
Am I her Shizuku-chan?
Are you for real?
I've never been someone's best girl!
I feel so happy I can literally explore right now!
Thanks Akira!
This is the greatest news of all time!
It means the world to me!
I'm like over the moon!
You have no idea what a huge honor this is!
I could cry!
Come on, Shinju!
Huh?
Take our freakin' pig!
To be honest, I didn't think anything good would ever happen to me.
Is this okay?
Do I deserve this?
Do I deserve to be happy?
Look here!
And smile big!
Oh, crap!
Are you okay?!
Don't be sweet to her!
You'll make her cry even more!
Stagawa!
Come stand over here where it's safe!
We so should've given you a heads up.
We're sorry, Maureen.
Aki is an enormous fan of yours.
I can guarantee you those are all happy tears.
Oh, I don't mind at all.
So there's no need to keep apologizing.
It's totally fine.
That one time we all went to karaoke,
it would've been too weird to send Aki home while we hung out.
Sounds strange,
but you're a celebrity to her and she idolizes you.
I feel like we used you to make her happy,
which is gross and weird when you think about it.
I'm super sorry.
Yeah, me too.
I don't think you guys used anybody.
I'm the one who invited Maureen.
Yeah, so chillax.
Truth is,
I had been all in my head about something,
but Akira pulled me out.
It was just the medicine I needed.
Plus, it taught me a great lesson.
You've got to tell people how you feel.
Duh!
I'm going to thank her one more time.
You need to keep a safe distance.
There's lesson two.
For all of our safety,
please stop planning surprises.
No more arguments on that front.
Thank you guys.
See ya.
Let's do it again.
See you.
See ya.
Bye bye for now.
I'll see you soon.
It's suddenly back to the two of us again.
Oh, yeah.
This is it.
Only three little words.
I just have to spit them out.
Oh, Mia.
Shortest train ever.
Kitagawa.
Yes?
Since we have so much stuff,
I can walk you home.
Tell the boy you love him already,
you goober!
Well,
if you're not too busy,
okay?
Mm-hmm.
I love you.
I love you, Kojo.
I...
I just can't do it.
Think you can handle it from here?
Yeah.
Sure.
Are you okay?
Of course I am!
You have the perfect view of the sunset.
It's so beautiful.
Kitagawa.
Thank you for including me in the group today.
I had a great time.
Sure, making your clothes is fun,
but so is making all your props.
If you're next cosplay,
it would be an interesting challenge
to create as many pieces for it as I possibly can.
I'm excited to see what the future brings.
Well, I should head on home.
See you at school.
Hang on!
Hey, so...
I, uh...
Should tell you that I...
Will you please...
Will you take a selfie with me?
Sure.
I would love to.
Really?
Uh...
Yeah.
Hey!
What's gotten into you?
Are you sure you're feeling okay?
I'm totally fine.
I'm just happy.
Quick, let's take it.
While we have the light.
Three...
Two...
Cheese!
The thickest totes of dorks!
Thank you for indulging me, Kojo.
That's very nice.
But you're embarrassing me,
Xtagawa!
It's very nice,
but you're embarrassing me,
Xtagawa!
It's very nice,
but you're embarrassing me,
Xtagawa!
You're embarrassing me, Xtagawa!
Wow!
Watching a film?
When it's OK,
it's very nice.
By the end ...
Me is like a livestream,
but you're in the poster.
Yeah.
I'm like how this is,
you're not real,
you're a hobby,
and sometimescolor into place.
Have you heardазд take care of it?
Freaky turn!
I'm like how this environment is deadly.
Do you know how she's robić?
How the strength to be within you?
How about you?
Kawaii isai wa
Toki, tokie, tokie
Ready? And...
Thank you very much!